Finding Aid for the Horace Marden Albright Papers LSC.2056
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Files on Various Topics
  - National Park Service: news clippings., 1955-56 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Coast National Park. (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Trip., 1957 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Air Force. (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - U.S. [ ] correspondence. (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Borax, miscellaneous papers. (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Congress on Los Angeles Watershed. (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - University of California - Alumni Affairs. (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - University of California - Congressman Greg Hosmer, UC alumnus. (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - University of California Riverside. (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - University of California correspondence. (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - University of California. (Box 272, Folder 6)
    Miscellaneous papers.
  - Wilderness, general. (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Printed papers, articles, news clippings. (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - HMA's Medal of Freedom., 1980 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    Photographs and letters of congratulations.
- Miscellaneous Publications
  - "A Study of the Profession of Landscape Architecture" - Albert Fein. (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - "The Sugar Tramp" - Dan Gutleben. Oxnard Sugar Beet Factory., 1961 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - "The Sugar Tramp" - Dan Gutleben. Ohio, MSG, Indiana, Illinois., 1963 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Report on First Williamsburg Student Burgesses., 1958 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Castaic Reservoir Recreation Development - Warren L. Down. (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. (Box 274, Folder 2-3)
  - U.S. Borax printed papers. (Box 274, Folder 4-5)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior. Conservation Yearbook., 1965 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - California Academy of Sciences. (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Santa Monica Mountains Study. Supplemental Report no.4. California Division of Beaches and Parks. (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - President's Departmental Reorganization Proposal. Department of Economic Affairs reports., March 1971 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Santa Fe Railway Company annual report., 1960 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous printed papers. (Box 275, Folder 6-7)
  - Miscellaneous printed papers. (Box 276, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous articles. (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous items. (Box 276, Folder 5)
- Books
  - Greene and Greene: Architects in the Residential Style. Current, Karen. Amon Carter Museum of Western Art., 1974 (Box 277)
  - Dredge, Drain, Reclaim. The Art of a Nation. Van Veen, Dr. J. Martinus Nyhoff. The Hague., 1952 (Box 277)
  - The Battle of the Floods [no author]. Netherlands Booksellers and Publishers Association Amsterdam., 1953 (Box 277)
  - Fifteen Thousand Miles By Stage. Strahorn, Carrie Adell. New York and London: Putnams., 1911 (Box 277)
  - The Woods and the Sea. Lunt, Dudley Cammett. New York: Knopf., 1965 (Box 277)
  - Scout Naturalists in the Rocky Mountains. Fast, Alger J., Boynton S. Kaiser, and Donald G. Kelley. New York: Brewer, Warren, and Putnam., 1932 (Box 277)
  - The Conservation of the Wildlife in Canada. Hewitt, C. Gordon. New York: Charles Scribner., 1921 (Box 277)
  - "Like a Fishhook: Village and Fort Berthold." Smith, G. Hubert. National Park Service Anthropological Papers (no.2). National Park Service, U.S. Department of the Interior. Washington., 1972 (Box 278)
  - Journey From the Arctic. Brown, D.C. New York: Knopf., 1956 (Box 278)
  - Birth of a National Park in the Great Smokey Mountains. Campbell, Carlos C. University of Tennessee., 1960 (Box 278)
    (preface by HMA)
  - El Sol del Rey. Hawkins, Walace. Austin: Texas State Historical Association., 1947 (Box 278)
  - Economic Theory of Natural Resources. Herfendahl, Orris C. and Allen V. Kneese. Columbus, Ohio: Resources for the Future, Incorporated, Charles E. Merrill., 1974 (Box 278)
  - "Archaeological Observations North of the Rio Colorado." Judd, Neil M. Smithsonian Institution, Bureau of American Ethnology Bulletin (no.32). Government Printing Office, Washington., 1906 (Box 278)
  - The Earth-Man Story. Lambert, Darwin. New York: Exposition Press., 1972 (Box 278)
  - Asian Dilemma: United States, Japan, and China. Burnell, Elaine H. Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. Santa Barbara, California., 1969 (Box 278)
  - Asian Dilemma: United States, Japan, and China. Burnell, Elaine H. Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. Santa Barbara, California., 1969 (Box 278)
  - Our Plundered Planet. Osborn, Fairfield. New York: Pyramid Books., 1968 (Box 278)
  - Soldier and Brave. New York: Harper and Row., 1963 (Box 279)
  - National Park Service, National Survey of Historic Sites and Buildings, vol.12. (Box 279)
  - "101 Trips to the Land of Enchantment." Woods, Betty. New Mexico Magazine. Santa Fe, New Mexico., 1965 (Box 279)
  - Representative Government and Land Management. Haefele, Edwin T. Johns Hopkins University Press for Resources for the Future., 1973 (Box 279)
  - "The Steamboat Bertrand. History, Excavation, Architecture." Petsche, Jerome E. National Park Service Publications in Archaeology (no.11). Government Printing Office: Washington D.C.., 1974 (Box 279)
  - "Reform as Reorganization." Wingo, Lowden, ed.; Governance of Metropolitan Regions series, no.4. Resources for the Future Washington, D.C.., 1974 (Box 279)
  - John Marshall. Bicentennial Celebration, 1955. Final Report of U.C. Commission for the Celebration of the Two Hundredth Anniversary of the Birth of John Marshall. Washington D.C. (Box 279)
- [Prints, Clippings, Articles, Miscellaneous]
  - Miscellaneous printed papers on National Parks. (Box 280)
  - Press clippings., 1910s-1970s (Box 281-289)
    - 1910s. (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - 1920s. (Box 281, Folder 2-5)
    - 1920s. (Box 282, Folder 1-4)
    - 1920s. (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
    - 1930s. (Box 283, Folder 3-5)
    - 1940s. (Box 284, Folder 1-4)
    - 1950s. (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - 1950s. (Box 285, Folder 1-4)
    - 1950s. (Box 286, Folder 1-4)
    - 1950s. (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - 1960s. (Box 287, Folder 2-4)
    - 1962-1966. (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - 1964-1966. (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - 1970s. (Box 288, Folder 3-5)
    - Saturday Evening Post. (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Jackson Hole Courier., 1930s-1950s (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Record. (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - New York Times., 1932-1933 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Tourist Tattler (vol.1-9), Yellowstone National Park. (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Magazine articles. (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Magazine articles. (Box 290, Folder 1-4)
  - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden, 2/3 correspondence. (Box 291)
  - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden. (Box 292)
  - National Parks Association. Includes National Parks Magazine, National Parks Bulletin. (Box 293)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company. (Box 294)
  - Council on Environmental Quality: 102 Monitor. (Box 294)
  - Bureau of Land Management: "Our Public Lands." (Box 294)
  - "News Beat." (Box 294)
  - National Wildlife Federation: Conservation News, National Wildlife Conservation Report. (Box 295)
  - The Nature Conservancy. (Box 296)
    Includes The Nature Conservancy News plus some correspondence.
  - Nomination of Governor of Alaska to be Secretary of the Interior (Congressional Hearings and Congressional Record)., 1969 (Box 297)
  - Rainbow Bridge Monument Valley Expedition., 1934 (Box 298)
  - James A. Russell and Russell White. (Box 298)
  - American Science and Historic Preservation Society. (Box 298)
  - California: Squaw Valley/Death Valley. (Box 299)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve. (Box 300)
  - American Conservation Association Pacific Pathways. (Box 301)
  - Wyoming, miscellaneous newspaper clippings. (Box 302)
  - Citizens' Committed on Natural Resources. (Box 303)
  - Rockefeller correspondence, Moral Rearmament, Charles E. Peterson. (Box 304)
  - Yellowstone Native Notes. (Box 305)
  - Yellowstone Native Notes, public meetings of Yellowstone. (Box 306)
  - Grand Teton Master Plan Study Team (Box 306)
  - Yellowstone/National Park Service. (Box 307)
  - Yellowstone/National Park Service, includes some correspondence. (Box 308)
  - News and Views, State of California Department of Natural Resources, Division of Beaches and Parks. (Box 309)
  - The Backlog, Camp Fire Club of America. (Box 309)
  - The Regional Review: National Park Service, Region 1. (Box 310)
  - Region 3 Quarterly: National Park Service. (Box 310)
  - The Branding Iron: Los Angeles Westerners' Corral. (Box 310)
  - Park Service Bulletin: National Park Service. (Box 311-312)
  - Yosemite Nature Notes. (Box 313)
  - California Monthly. (Box 314-315)
  - The USP Pioneer. U.S. Potash Company. (Box 316-317)
  - Forest History: Forest History Society. (Box 318)
  - Landscape Architecture: American Society of Landscape Architects. (Box 318)
  - The Architectural Forum. (Box 318)
  - The Dude Rancher: Dude Ranchers' Association. (Box 319)
  - The Blue Book of Western Dude Ranches. (Box 319)
  - Animal Kingdom: Bulletin of the New York Zoological Society. (Box 319)
  - Natural Resources of U.S. States. U.S. Department of the Interior. (Box 319)
  - California Alumni Fortnightly: Alumni Association of the University of California, Berkeley, California. (Box 319)
  - The School of American Research. Santa Fe, New Mexico. (Box 320)
  - Natural History: American Museum of Natural History. (Box 320)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation Quarterly. (Box 320)
  - Announcer: Monthly Review of the Philips Industries. (Box 320)
  - Environment: Committee for Environmental Information. (Box 320)
  - Appalachian Trailway News: Appalachian Trail Conference. (Box 320)
  - Progress. The Magazine of [ ]. (Box 321)
  - New Mexico Sun Trails: Tourist Industries Council of New Mexico. (Box 321)
  - Science Newsletter: Weekly summary of current science. (Box 321)
  - The Rotarian: Rotary International. (Box 321)
  - The Otter Raft. Friends of the Sea Otter. (Box 321)
  - Communique. News of the Professional and Citizens Branches of the National Recreation and Park Association. (Box 321)
  - Think: IBM. (Box 321)
  - The Freeman. A Fortnightly for Individualists. (Box 321)
  - The Outlook. An Illustrated Weekly of Current Life. (Box 321)
  - Outers' Recreation. The Magazine That Brings the Outdoors In. (Box 321)
  - Mills Quarterly/Mills Magazine: Mills College, Oakland, California. (Box 321)
  - The Conservationist. State of New York Conservation Department. (Box 321)
  - The Center Magazine. Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. (Box 321)
  - U.S. News and World Report. (Box 322)
  - Miscellaneous journals. (Box 322)
  - The Condor. Magazine of Western Ornithology. (Box 322)
  - Outdoor America. Izaak Walton League of America. (Box 322)
  - Outdoor Life Sportman's Magazine of the West. (Box 322)
  - Miscellaneous magazines. (Box 323-326)
  - Miscellaneous., 1928, 1931, 1932 and 1959 (Box 327)
    Includes air view of Dakota Badlands, September 1932
    Also, Cosmos Club Lists of Members, 1928, 1931, 1959.
  - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources. (Box 328-330)
  - First World Conference on National Parks, Seattle., 1962 (Box 328-330)
  - National Park Service: mainly press releases, some minutes of staff meetings. (Box 331-337)
  - National Park Service: pamphlet guides to properties. (Box 338-339)
  - National Park Service Natural History Handbook Series. (Box 340)
  - Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission Study Report. (Box 341-343)
  - Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government. (Box 344)
  - Conservation. American Forestry Association. (Box 344)
  - Planning and Civic Government. American Planning and Civic Association. (Box 345-347)
  - Sierra Club Bulletin. (Box 348-354)
    Box 354 includes Sierra Club Circular and National News Report.
  - Historic Preservation. Quarterly of National Trust for Historic Preservation. (Box 355)
  - Cry California. The Journal of California Tomorrow. (Box 356)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Annual Reports. (Box 356)
  - Annals of Wyoming/Quarterly Bulletin, Wyoming State Department of History. (Box 356)
  - National Park Service Popular Study Series. (Box 356)
  - History 1-14. (Box 356)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation, Incorporated. (Box 357)
  - Corral Dust. Potomac Corral of Westerners Southwestern Monuments Reports; National Park Service. (Box 357)
  - The Argonaut. Atlantic Chapter of Sierra Club. (Box 357)
  - Canada. (Box 358)
  - Bulletin of the Fort Ticonderoga Museum. (Box 358)
  - El Palacio. Quarterly Journal of the Museum of New Mexico. (Box 358)
  - Horace M. Albright Conservation Lectureship. 1-5, 8, 10. (Box 359)
  - Plateau. Quarterly of Museum of Northern Arizona. (Box 359)
  - Population Bulletin. Population Reference Bureau, Incorporated. (Box 359)
  - National Wildlands News. (Box 359)
  - Bulletin of the Associated Mountaineering Clubs of North America. (Box 359)
  - Miscellaneous journals, monographs, reports, and articles. (Box 360-371)
  - Books (by Adrian Van Sinderen in 372-374 and in 375). (Box 372-378)
  - Albert National Park, Belgian Congo., (20 Prints) (Box 384, Folder 8)
  - Albuquerque Journal., February 16, 1951 (Box 380, Folder 1)
  - Anaconda Standard., June 18, 1927 (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - Asheville Citizen Times., March 26, 1950 (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - Bawl Street Journal., June 8, 1956 (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - Berkeley Daily Gazette., May 12, 1948 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Bozeman Courier., June 18 and July 16, 1926 (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - Calico Print., July 1950; January-April and August 1951 (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - Capitol in Story and Pictures., 1955-1956 (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - Casper Daily Tribune & Weekly Review., January 22, 1922; March 5 and 15, 1924; March 29, 1926 (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - Christian Science Monitor., March 16, 1966 (Box 379, Folder 6)
  - Cody Enterprise., March 11, 1936 (Box 379, Folder 7)
  - Daily Current-Argus. Carlsbad, New Mexico., February 11, 1951 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - Daily Enterprise. Livington, Montana., June 4, 1882; (2 copies of vol.1, no.1) (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Daily Mail., April 25, 1959 (Box 379, Folder 8)
  - Denver Post, The. "This Week Magazine.", August 11, 1957 (Box 380, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Defense Fund. Michigan Department of Agriculture. (Box 385, Folder 4)
  - Evening News, The. London., December 5, 1955 (Box 379, Folder 9)
  - Flushing Meadow And Beyond - Preliminary Report On A Proposal. (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Franconia Notch State Park, New Hampshire, A Master Development. (Box 384, Folder 3)
    A master development plan.
  - Gatlinburg Press., June 11, 1964 (Box 379, Folder 10)
  - Great Falls Tribune., October 25, 1925 (Box 380, Folder 7)
  - Inyo Register., April 29, 1965; June 13, 1971 (Box 379, Folder 11)
  - Jackson Hole Guide, The., September 18, 1952 (Box 379, Folder 12)
  - Knoxville Journal., April 5, 1953 (Box 379, Folder 13)
  - Livingston Enterprise., 1923-1938 (Box 383, Folder 1-10)
    - June 7 and 20, July 19, 24, 27 and 28-29, August 8-10, 12, 15-19, 21-23, 25-26 and 28-31, September 1, 2, 5-8, 16 and 23, 1923. (Box 383, Folder 1-10)
    - June 12, 20, 22, 25-27, 29; July 1-2, 12, 15-16, 19, 23, 29-31; August 1-3, 6-9, 17, 19, 23-24, 27, 30 September 4, 9-11, 1924. (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - June 18 and August 28, 1925. (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - June 13, 18, 20, 22, 23, 25, 29, 30; July 1, 3, 4, 7, 8, 20, 24; August 24 and October 29, 1926. (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - June 17 and 19, 1927. (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - June 20, 1928. (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - September 13, 1929. (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - June 20, 1933. (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - June 20, 1937. (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - June 15, 1938. (Box 383, Folder 10)
  - London Times., September 16, 1950; December 8, 1955 (Box 379, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Record., July 31, 1924 (Box 380, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Times., January 2, 1959 (Box 380, Folder 9)
  - - Motoring Section, Outdoors., Los Angeles Times April 16, 1933 (Box 379, Folder 15)
  - Reproduction of 1839 map of the U.S. By David H. Burr., 1954 (Box 385, Folder 3)
  - Mariposa Gazette., April 1, 1927 (Box 379, Folder 16)
  - Montana Business Monitor, Livingston., January 1926 (Box 380, Folder 10)
  - National Editors' Argus., July 12, 1922 (Box 380, Folder 11)
  - National Geographic Map of Proposed Redwood National Park., July 1966; (Poster) (Box 384, Folder 7)
  - National Parks Of The Belgian Congo (Photographs). (Box 385, Folder 5)
  - New York Herald Tribune., April 13, 1936; October 3, 1950; April 20, 1951; April 4, 1954; November 30, 1958 (Box 379, Folder 17)
  - New York Journal American., April 18, 1951 (Box 379, Folder 18)
  - New York Times., July 14, 1933; October 1, 30, 1950 (Box 379, Folder 19)
  - New York Times - Magazine., June 7, 1959 (Box 380, Folder 12)
  - Oakland Tribune., September 20, 1925; August 22, 1926 (Box 380, Folder 13)
  - Ocean Times., November 2, 1950 (Box 379, Folder 20)
  - Park County News., July 17, 1925; September 4, 18, 1958; August 17, 27, 1959; September 3, 10, 17; April 29, 1965; n.d. (Box 379, Folder 21)
  - Pictorial Forest Lawn., 1953 (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Pony Express, The. Sonora, California., May 1957 (Box 380, Folder 14)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch., March 31, 1957 (Box 380, Folder 15)
  - Sacramento Union., January 24, 25, 1948 (Box 379, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Chronicle., February 16, 1925 (Box 380, Folder 16)
  - San Francisco Examiner., August 23, 1931 (Box 379, Folder 23)
  - Santa Fe New Mexican., September 1, 1944 (Box 380, Folder 17)
  - Scotsman, The. Edinburgh., August 28 and September 5, 1950 (Box 379, Folder 24)
  - Sheridan Journal., March 25, 1926 (Box 380, Folder 18)
  - Standard-Star, The. New Rochelle, New York., April 21, 1961 (Box 380, Folder 19)
  - Steve Mather's Family Newspaper. Published by the employees and alumni association of the National Parks Service., September 1, 1957 (Box 379, Folder 25)
  - Stockton Record. "Out O'-Doors" Section and/or Daily., 1924-1932 (Box 381-382)
    - January 5, 19, 26; February 2, 9, 16, 23; March 1, 8, 15, 22, 29; April 5, 12, 22, 26; May 3, 10, 24, 31; June 7; July 12, 19; August 16; September 13, 27; October 11, 18; November 1, 29; and December 16, 1924. (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - January 3, 5, 10, 17, 31; February 7, 14, 21, 18; March 7, 14, 21, 28; April 4, 11, 18, 25; May 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; June 6, 13 and 20, 1925. (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - July 4; August 8, 15; September 19, 26; October 3, 10, 17, 24, 31; November 7, 14, 21, 28; December 5, 12, 19 and 24, 1925. (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - January 2, 9, 24, 30; February 6, 13, 20, 27; March 13, 20; April 3, 10, 17, 24; May 1, 8, 15, 22, 29; June 5, 12, 19 and 26, 1926. (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - July 3, 10, 19, 24, 31; August 14; September 4, 11, 25; October 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; November 6, 13, 20, 27; December 4, 11, 18 and 25, 1926. (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - January 1, 8, 15, 22, 29; February 5, 12, 19, 26; March 5, 19, 29; April 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; May 7, 14, 21, 28; June 11, 18 and 26, 1927. (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - July 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; August 6, 13, 20, 27; September 3, 10, 17, 24; October 1, 8, 15, 22 and 28, 1927. (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - July 23, 1928. (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - October 12; November 30; December 7 and 14, 1929. (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - January 11; March 29; May 17; June 21; July 5, 12, 19, 26; August 2, 9, 16, 23, 30; September 7, 20 and October 4, 1930. (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - March 1, 21, 28; June 13, 20, 27; July 4, 11, 18, 25; August 1, 8, 15, 22; September 5, 26; November 14 and December 12, 1931. (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - November 12 and December 24, 1932. (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - October 13, November 3, December 8, 15 and 22, 1923. (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Sunday Star. Washington, D.C., 1919, 1930-1933 (Box 380, Folder 20)
    - Sunday Star. Washington, D.C., March 9, 16, 1930; December 6, 1931; February 26 and July 16, 1933 (Box 380, Folder 20)
    - June 15, 1919; January 19, 26, February 16, 23, March 16 and May 25, 1930; July 16, 1933. (Box 380, Folder 21)
  - Territorial Enterprise., September 5, 1958 (Box 379, Folder 26)
  - Texas State Parks. (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Trees for the Great - Honoring Carl Alvin Schenk. (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Geological Survey., 1914 (Box 384, Folder 6, 9-12)
    Atlases and a survey.
    - Atlas to Accompany Monograph 32 on the Geology of Yellowstone Park. By Arnold Hague, Washington., 1914 (Box 384, Folder 12)
      Monograph 32 is in collection 1444 (Box 97).
    - Atlas to Accompany the Tertiary History of Grand Canyon District. By Clarence E. Dutton. (Box 384, Folder 9)
      Monograph which accompanies this is in collection 1444 (Box 184).
    - Geological Atlas of the U.S. Lassen Peak Folio, California., 1895 (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - Geological Survey of the U.S. Devil's Tower Folio, Wyoming., 1897 (Box 384, Folder 11)
    - Monograph no.2., 1882 (Box 384, Folder 10)
  - Visalia Times-Daily., May 25, 1951 (Box 379, Folder 27)
  - Washington Post., March 9, 1930 and July 16, 1933 (Box 379, Folder 28)
  - White's City Daily News., November 15, 1940 and October 6, 1942 (Box 379, Folder 29)
  - World's Fair Program. (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming State Tribune., June 14-15, 1933 (Box 379, Folder 30)